affiliateshop.com 2017-12-13

# AffiliateShop - Privacy Policy

SilkRoad technology, inc. considers your privacy important. This policy explains our policies and practices regarding how we use and disclose personal information that you provide to us. By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information by us.

This Web site is owned and controlled by SilkRoad technology, inc. 111 N Chestnut, Winston-Salem, NC 27101, USA.

SilkRoad is committed to implementing measures designed to protect the privacy of those using our services. Although SilkRoad respects the privacy of all those who visit our site and use our online services, we do collect information from and about our users. Except as set forth within this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service (as the same may be amended and updated from time to time), we do not release personally identifiable information (as described below) about users of this site without their permission.

Effect of This and Related Documents: This Privacy Policy, together with our Terms of Service, governs your interaction with this site, and your registration for and use of SilkRoad's online services.

Periodic Policy Changes: Please note that SilkRoad reviews its privacy practices from time to time, and that those practices are subject to change. We ask that you bookmark and periodically review this page to ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our privacy policy.

Opt-Out Option: If you would like to have your personally-identifiable information removed from SilkRoad's databases going forward, please call 888.329.3363, or email  [info@silkroadtech.com](mailto:info@silkroadtech.com), and we will use reasonable efforts to comply with your request. However, there will be residual information that will remain within SilkRoad's databases, access logs, and other historical internal records, which may or may not contain such personally-identifiable information.

### The Information We May Gather

  1. Non-personally-identifiable information:

(a) General: When users come to our site, we collect and aggregate information indicating their home server, but not their e-mail addresses. Such information helps us identify the most popular content and portions of our site and determine the effectiveness of our various promotional activities. We aggregate such information for internal review and thereafter it's superseded by more recent information.

(b) "Cookies": We also use "cookies" -- that is, small text files placed on your computer's hard drive -- to help you in getting faster access to this site's contents, and to help us determine the type of content you find of interest and the sites to which you link, the length of time you spend at any particular area of this site, and the particular SilkRoad services you choose to use. Cookies are only read by the server that placed them, and are unable to execute any code or virus. Cookies allow SilkRoad to serve you better, and to personalize your Web-browsing experience. Nevertheless, you should be able to control how and whether cookies will be accepted by your Web browser. For more information on how to do this, please refer to the documentation accompanying your browser or third party Web sites. 

  2. Personally Identifiable Information:

(a) General: In certain areas of this site, we require that you provide us with personally-identifiable information, in order to be able to use that portion or those portions of this site. For instance, the names and contact information of persons who visit our Web sites are added to our data base (presently maintained in Winston-Salem, North Carolina, USA) so that, for example, they may be contacted in the future regarding SilkRoad's products, services or future opportunities. Such contact may occur by email, telephone or mail, as SilkRoad deems appropriate.

(b) Lack of SilkRoad Responsibility For Third Party Content On site: SilkRoad cannot and does not control the acts of the users of its Web site's services or monitor the accuracy of postings by such users. All users should be aware that, when they disclose personally identifiable information in a bulletin board, chat room, or other forum or public area of this site, the information might be collected, circulated, and used by others. In the event that you encounter any user who is improperly collecting or using information about you or other users, please contact us at 888.329.3363, or email 

[info@silkroadtech.com](mailto:info@silkroadtech.com). 

### How We Use The Information We Gather

  1. How We Use Non-Personally Identifiable Information: We aggregate data on users' home servers for internal review purposes, in order to build higher quality, more useful online services and better products, e.g., by performing statistical analyses of the collective characteristics and behavior of our users. Following such internal review, such aggregated information is then superseded by more recent information. 
  2. How We Use Personally-Identifiable Information: SilkRoad provides notice to users that personally-identifiable (i.e., non-aggregated) information will be collected during the Web-browsing process; this Privacy Policy also serves as notice that such information is collected under those circumstances. SilkRoad may use such information to enhance your experience by providing such information to third parties, including any outsourcers, as reviewed and selected by SilkRoad. 

SilkRoad reserves the right to disclose information contained in our access logs concerning any user as we reasonably feel is necessary to protect our systems or business. In particular, we reserve the right to disclose such when a user is in violation of our current or later Terms of Service or other published guidelines, or initiates or participates in (or suspected of) any illegal activity, even without a subpoena, warrant, or other court order, and to disclose such information in response to court and governmental orders, civil subpoenas, discovery requests, and as otherwise required by law.

In reviewing the information above, please keep in mind that SilkRoad cannot and does not assume any responsibility for any actions or omissions of third parties, including other site users, including the manner in which they might use information received either from SilkRoad or independently.

Terms and Copyright

### Terms of Service

This W[eb site](http://www.silkroadtech.com/) (and all sub-domains) ("Web site") is owned and maintained by SilkRoad technology, inc. ("SilkRoad"). By accessing this Web site or any materials or services provided by SilkRoad through this Web site, you agree to the terms and provisions of these Terms of Service (“TOS”). If you do not agree to these TOS, do not access or use this Web site. If you are accessing this Web site on behalf of your employer, you represent that you are authorized to accept these TOS on your employer’s behalf. SilkRoad may change these TOS at any time by posting the revised TOS on this Web site and you agree to review these TOS periodically to be aware of such change. Your continued use of this Web site after any changes to these TOS are posted will mean you accept such changes. If you do not agree to these TOS or any modified TOS at any time, immediately cease using this Web site. SilkRoad reserves the right to modify or discontinue any feature or services available on this Web site at any time.

### Copyright & Trademark Information

Except where noted otherwise, all content published via SilkRoad Web Properties is the property of SilkRoad technology, inc.

Copyright 2003 - 2005 SilkRoad technology, inc. All rights reserved. Any reproduction or distribution of SilkRoad Web site content without the permission of SilkRoad technology, inc. is prohibited. Information on the SilkRoad internal Web site may not be copied or distributed without explicit written permission of SilkRoad.

SilkRoad technology, inc, [www.silkroadtech.com](http://www.silkroadtech.com/), the ribbon logo, AffiliateShop, ChatBlazer, Eprise, Fuse, NetAnswer, OpenHire, OpinionWare,   Pendulab, ReadyEdit, SilkBlogs, SilkBlogs _Mobile_ , SilkDocs, SilkMob, SilkPolls, SilkQuizes, SilkSurveys, SilkWare, TrueLook, the respective taglines, logos and service marks are trademarks of SilkRoad technology, Inc., which may be registered in certain jurisdictions. All other trademarks are owned by their respective owners. Some or all of the information contained in this Web site may be protected by patents pending application for SilkRoad technology, inc.

THE INFORMATION AND CONTENT PROVIDED ON THIS WEB SITE ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NON-INFRINGEMENT. THE CONTENT OF THIS WEB SITE MAY CONTAIN INACCURATE OR TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS AND SILKROAD MAY MAKE IMPROVEMENTS OR CHANGES TO THE CONTENT AT ANY TIME.

For further information regarding SilkRoad trademarks and copyrights, please contact  [info@silkroadtech.com](mailto:info@silkroadtech.com)
